

#### **INFO**

Amel BOUGRINE Age Situation Single Mobility International Work-Place In Office or Remote

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Ability To Work Under Pressure

Problem Solving

Adaptability

Attention To Detail

Fast Learning

#### LANGUAGES

Arabic French English German

# CONTACT -



# Front End Developer & UI/UX Designer -

Hard-working, self-educated Front-End Developer, had changed my career after almost five years in Electrical Engineering and Management to specialize in Web Development.

Skilled in coding, debugging and UX design, completed different projects on GitHub, and I am looking to join a motivated team to work on interesting projects and deliver coding excellence.

#### **Programming Skills**

Technology	Framework/Library	Tools	Database
HTML5/CSS3	JQuery	Ajax/JSON	MySQL
JavaScript ES6	Bootstrap	Gulp/Babel	MongoDB
NodeJs/Express	Sass	Git/Github	
C#/.Net	React/Redux	Ubuntu/CLI	

# **Work Experience**

#### Freelance - Ecommerce Web App

Fairlight 365 - United Kingdom

Build a B2B ecommerce solution using the Dynamicweb CMS Platform with real-time Microsoft Dynamics ERP integration.

(\) 04/2010 - 06/2021 (\overline{\pi}) Remote Work (\overline{\pi}) C#/.net core- RAZOR Pages

#### Freelance – Data Visualization App

Fairlight 365 - United Kingdom

Create an Office Integration Solution in which the user can set up visualization tools on Excel Online to generate automatic dashboards that track company performance across key indicators and visually interpret the results.

(1) 11/2010 – 02/2021 • Remote Work • Ts – Xml – Html – Css – OfficeJs Api

#### Internship - UI/UX Design

WonderKid - Sousse Tunisia

Design an E-commerce website that helps creative kids to sell their handmade product and grow their online business, the goal was to provide great user experience in order to convince visitors to make a purchase and convince creative kids to become sellers.

### Internship - Web Design & Digital Marketing

Create a responsive showcase website for Language Training Center and develop a marketing and branding strategy.

(\) 05/2020 - 07/2020

# **Education**

#### **Web Development Training**

Web Design, Responsive Design

National Program TUNICOD: Talent Accelerator

(L) 10/2019 - 01/2020 • Online • Q Certified

# **National Engineering Diploma in Electrical Engineering**

**National School of Engineers of Monastir** 

Specialty: Industrial Information Technology.

( 2010 – 2013 Monastir, Tunisia Diploma

#### **Bachelor in Electronics**

**Higher Institute of Applied Sciences and Technology of Gafsa** 

Specialty: Automatics for industrial systems.

( C) 2007 – 2010 ( C) Gafsa, Tunisia ( Diploma